Miklos Rozsa Papers
Miklos Rozsa Papers
- Commercial recordings
  - Compact discs
    - Symphony in 3 Movements, op. 6a, The Vintner's Daughter, op. 23a, James Sedares, New Zealand Symphony Orchestra, 1994; KOCH International Classics 3-7244-2H1 (Box 70)
    - Thief of Baghdad / Jungle Book: Original Motion Picture Scores, 1990; Colosseum Schallplatten CST 34.8044 (Box 70)
    - Time After Time: Original Motion Picture Score, 1987; Fifth Continent Music SCCD 1014 (Box 70)
    - Viklarbo Chamber Ensemble, Schieckele, Dahl, Freund, Rózsa, 1994; Raptoria RCD 1005 (Box 70)
    - Warriors of the Silver Screen, 1997; Silva Screen Records FILMXCD 187 (Box 70)
  - Phonograph records
    - 3 Chamber Works: Op. 8 Duo for Cello and Piano, Op. 36 Toccata Capricciosa, Op. 15a Sonata for Two Violins, 1978; Entr'acte Recording Society ERS 6009 (Oversize 348)
    - 3 Choral Works: Op. 20 To Everything There is a Season, Op. 30 The Vanities of Life, Op. 34 23rd Psalm, 1978; Entr'acte Recording Society ERS 6512 (Oversize 348)
    - A Time To Love and A Time To Die, 1976; MCA VIM 7204 (Oversize 348)
    - Albert Dominguez Plays Miklós Rózsa and Mario Catelnuovo-Tedesco, Orion Master Recordings ORS 74137 (Oversize 348)
    - Ballerina, Part 1 and Part 2, 1952; MGM Pictures (Oversize 348)
    - Ballerina, Part 3 and Part 3, 1952; MGM Pictures (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, MGM M/MS 503 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, MGM S1E1 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, MGM S1E1 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, MGM 1E1 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, More Music, MGM E3900 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, National Philharmonic Orchestra, 1977; Decca SPC 21166 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, National Philharmonic Orchestra, England, 1977; Decca PFS 4394 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, Volume 1, MGM Select 2353 030 (Oversize 348)
    - Ben-Hur, Volume 2, MGM Select 2353 075 (Oversize 348)
    - Bernstein: Backgrounds for Brando, Dot DLP 3107 (Oversize 348)
    - Blood on the Sun, Citadel Records CT-6031 (Oversize 348)
    - Blood on the Sun, Citadel Records CT-6031 (Oversize 348)
    - Blood on the Sun, "Jap Cafe" and "Harakiri", Electro-Vox Recording Studio, copy (Oversize 348)
    - Brute Force and Naked City, Tony Thomas Productions TT-MR-3 (Oversize 348)
    - Carole Dawn Reinhart, Trompete, Germany, 1973; Polydor International 2555 008 (Oversize 348)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco and Strauss, Heifetz, 1956; RCA Victor LM 2050 (Oversize 348)
    - Chopin Waltzes, Leonard Pennario, 1980; Angel DS 37332 (Oversize 348)
    - Cinderella, Columbia OS 2730 (Oversize 348)
    - Classic Film Music, 1987; Colosseum Schallplatten CST 8027-2 (Oversize 348)
    - Concerto for Strings, 1951; Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 348)
    - Concerto for Strings, RCA Victor RR 18410 (Oversize 348)
    - Concerto for Strings, Electro-Vox Recording Studio (Oversize 348)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, Piano Version, Electro-Vox Recording Studio, copy (Oversize 348)
    - Concerto for Violoncello and Orchestra, Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 348)
    - Concertos Under the Stars, Hollywood Bowl Symphony Orchestra, Capitol P 8326 (Oversize 348)
    - Contemporary Piano Sonatas, Bartok, Prokofiev, Rózsa, Capitol P 8376 (Oversize 348)
    - Danube Waves, Hollywood Bowl Symphony Orchestra, Capitol P 8540 (Oversize 348)
    - David, Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 348)
    - Digital Space, London Symphony Orchestra, 1979; Varèse Sarabande Records VCDM 1000.20 (Oversize 348)
    - Double Life, Medallion ML 314 (Oversize 348)
    - Double Life, Medallion ML 314 (Oversize 348)
    - Double Life, "Main Title", Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 348)
    - Duo for Violin and Piano, Audiodisc Recording Blank (Oversize 348)
    - El Cid, 1986; MCA 25005 (Oversize 349)
    - El Cid, MGM Select 2353 046 (Oversize 349)
    - El Cid, MGM Select 2353 046 (Oversize 349)
    - Epic Film Scores: Quo Vadis, King of Kings, Ben-Hur, El Cid, England, 1967; Cloud Nine Records CN 7013 (Oversize 349)
    - Eye of the Needle, 1981; Varèse Sarabande Records STV 81133 (Oversize 349)
    - Eye of the Needle, Japan, 1981; Victor VIP 28028 (Oversize 349)
    - Eye of the Needle (Die Nadel), Germany, 1981; Celine Records CL 0003 (Oversize 349)
    - Eye of the Needle (L'Arme a L'oeil), France, 1981; Varèse Sarabande Records A 120 136 (Oversize 349)
    - Fedora, 1979; Varèse Sarabande Records STV 81108 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Music for Piano: Rózsa, Steiner, Korngold, 1979; Citadel Records CT 7010 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Music of Miklós Rózsa: The Power, Sodom and Gomorrah, Citadel Records CT-MR-1 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Music of Miklós Rózsa: The Power, Sodom and Gomorrah, Citadel Records CT-MR-1 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Conducted by the Composer, High Street Station Records 3301 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Music of Miklós Rózsa Conducted by the Composer, High Street Station Records 3301 (Oversize 349)
    - Film Spectacular Volume 4: The Epic, London Records SP 44173 (Oversize 349)
    - [The] Golden Voyage of Sinbad, England, 1974; United Artists Records UAS 29576 (Oversize 349)
    - Great Epic Film Themes, Sunset SLS 50243 (Oversize 349)
    - Great Movie Themes Composed by Miklós Rózsa, 1968; MFP 5232 (Oversize 349)
    - Green Fire: "Latin American" Instrumental, 1954; MGM Pictures (Oversize 349)
    - Heifetz-Rózsa Concert for Violin and Orchestra, 1964; RCA Victor LSC 2767 (Oversize 349)
    - Heifetz-Piatigorsky Concerts: Beethoven, Haydn, Rózsa, RCA Victor LM 2770 (Oversize 349)
    - Hungarian Serenade and The Vintner's Daughter, 1976; Citadel CT 6001 Test Pressing (Oversize 349)
    - Immortal Film Music of Miklós Rózsa, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, England, 1984; Memoir Records MOIR 101 (Oversize 349)
    - Ivanhoe, "The Battle of Torquilstone Castle," "Rebecca's Love," "Finale", Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 349)
    - John Crown, Pianist, Allan Hancock Foundation (Oversize 349)
    - Johnny Ever Greens Played By Russell Garcia, ABC-Paramount ABC 147 (Oversize 349)
    - Julius Caesar, 1986; MCA 25022 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book, Electro-Vox Recording Studios, copy (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book, Part 1 and Finale, RCA Victor DM 905-1 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book, Part 2 and Part 5, RCA Victor DM 905-2 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book, Part 3 and Part 4, RCA Victor DM 905-3 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book (Das Dschungelbuch), Germany, 1981; Colosseum Schallplatten SM 6602 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book (Das Dschungelbuch) and Thief of Baghdad (Der Dieb von Baghdad), Germany, 1983; Celine Records CL 0017 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book and Blind Flight, Electro-Vox Recording Studios, copy (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book and Thief of Baghdad, 1957; RCA Victor LM 2118 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book Suite & Thief of Baghdad Suite, England, 1957; United Artists Records UAS 29725 (Oversize 349)
    - Jungle Book Suite (& concertos by Waxman & Webb), 1979; Entr'acte Recording Society ERM 6002 (Oversize 349)
    - Kaleidoscope Suite, USC Hancock Foundation (Oversize 350)
    - [The] Killers, Parts 14-17, 1946; Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 350)
    - [The] Killers, Parts 1-7, 1946; Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 350)
    - King of Kings, 1961; MGM Select 2353 035 (Oversize 350)
    - King of Kings, MGM S1E2 (Oversize 350)
    - King of Kings, Robert Ryan Reads from the New Testament, MGM E3970 (Oversize 350)
    - Knights of the Round Table, 1980; Varèse Sarabande Records STV 81128 (Oversize 350)
    - Last Embrace, 1983; Varèse Sarabande Records STV 81166 (Oversize 350)
    - Leonard Bernstein's New York Philharmonic Debut, 1983; Monaural 831/2 (Oversize 350)
    - Liberace Plays Concert by Candlelight, England, 1966; Hallmark Records HM 518 (Oversize 350)
    - [The] Lost Weekend, Tony Thomas Productions TT-MR-2 (Oversize 350)
    - Lust For Life Suite, Background to Violence, Decca DL 10015 (Oversize 350)
    - Lust For Life Suite, Background to Violence, Decca DL 10015 (Oversize 350)
    - M.G.M. Studio Orchestra, Music From The Original Soundtrack Recordings of the M.G.M. Films: Ivanhoe, Plymouth Adventure, Madame Bovary, MGM Select 2353 095 (Oversize 350)
    - Madame Bovary, Elmer Bernstein's Filmmusic Collection FMC 12 (Oversize 350)
    - Madame Bovary, "Bovary Waltz", 1949 (Oversize 350)
    - Madame Bovary, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, Elmer Bernstein's Filmmusic Collection FMC 12 (Oversize 350)
    - Miklós Rózsa conducts his Great Film Music: Ben-Hur, Quo Vadis, El Cid, King of Kings, 1973; Angel S-36063 (Oversize 350)
    - Miklós Rózsa Conducts His Great Film Music, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, England, Polydor Super 2383 327 (Oversize 350)
    - Miklós Rózsa Conducts His Great Film Music, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, England, Polydor Super 2383 327 (Oversize 350)
    - Miklós Rózsa Conducts His Great Themes from Ben-Hur, El Cid, Quo Vadis and King of Kings, Capitol T 2837 (Oversize 350)
    - More Great M.G.M. Film Themes, MGM Select 2353 092 (Oversize 350)
    - Music for Films: The Killers, Dark Waters, Time Out of Mind, Tony Thomas Productions TT-MR-4 (Oversize 350)
    - Music for Films: The Killers, Dark Waters, Time Out of Mind, Tony Thomas Productions TT-MR-4 (Oversize 350)
    - Music from the Movies, England, 1980; EMI Records ASD 3862 (Oversize 350)
    - Music from the Soundtracks of Ivanhoe, Plymouth Adventure, Madame Bovary, MGM E3507 ST (Oversize 350)
    - Music of Miklós Rózsa: "Spellbound Concerto," "New England Concerto," "The World, The Flesh and The Devil," "Because of Him", 1985; Varèse Sarabande Digital 704.260 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 02 Piano Quintet, Op. 1 String Trio, Orion Master Recordings ORS 75191 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 07 Duo, Op. 5 Little Suite, Op. 4 Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song, Orion Master Recordings ORS 73127 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 07 Duo, Op. 5 Little Suite, Op. 4 Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song, England, 1975; Ember ECL 9043 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 17 Concerto for String Orchestra, MGM String Orchestra, MGM E3565 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 19b Kaleidoscope, Op. 5 North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, Op. 39 Sonata for Solo Flute, Op. 40 Sonata for Solo Violin, England, 1987; Cloud Nine Records CN 6001 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 19b Kaleidoscope, Op. 5 North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, Op. 39 Sonata for Solo Flute, Op. 40 Sonata for Solo Violin, England, 1987; Cloud Nine Records CN 6001 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 23, The Vintner's Daughter, Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 23a The Vintner's Daughter, Op. 5 North-Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, Op. 25 Hungarian Serenade, MGM SE 3645 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 25 Hungarian Serenade, Op. 23 The Vintner's Daughter, Citadel CT 6001 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 26 Concert Overture, Op. 14 Three Hungarian Sketches, Op. 13 Theme, Variations and Finale, Decca DL 9966 (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 29, Sinfonia Concertante for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 350)
    - Op. 31, Piano Concerto, Op. 2 Cello Concerto, Germany, 1982; Pantheon Music International FSM 53 901 PAN (Oversize 350)
    - Pastoral, Hollywood Bowl, Radio Recorders Inc. (Oversize 351)
    - Providence, 1980; DRG Records SL 9502 (Oversize 351)
    - Providence, France, 1978; Pema Music 900 057 (Oversize 351)
    - Providence, France, 1978; Pema Music 900 057 (Oversize 351)
    - Providence, France, 1977; EMI C 066 14406 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, "Hail Nero" (fast tempo), "Assyrian Dance", MGM Pictures, rehearsal (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, "Lygia", Johnny Green and his Orchestra, MGM 30526-B (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, "Triumphal March", MGM 30778 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, Dramatic Highlights, MGM E 134 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, 1978; Decca SPC 21180 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, 1978; Decca SPC 21180 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, Royal Philharmonic Orchestra and Chorus, England, 1978; Decca PFS 4430 (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis, Suite, 1952; Electro-Vox Recording Studios, dub (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis Suite, Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 351)
    - Quo Vadis?, 1953; Capitol, proof (Oversize 351)
    - Raintree Country, 1958; RCA Victor LOC 6000 (Oversize 351)
    - Raintree Country, 1976; Enrt'acte ERS 6503-ST (Oversize 351)
    - [The] Red House, 1947; Capitol Records CB 48 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa Conducts Rózsa: Concert Overture, Three Hungarian Sketches, Theme, Variations and Finale, 1978; Varèse International VC 81058 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa Conducts Rózsa: Julius Caesar, Lady Hamilton, The Killers, Lydia, Private Life of Sherlock Holmes, Five Graves to Cairo, Red Danube, England, 1977; Polydor UK Super 2383440 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa Conducts Rózsa: Op. 17 Concerto for String Orchestra, Op. 19a Kaleidoscope, Op. 4 Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song for Violin and Orchestra, 1977; ABC Records WG 8353 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa Conducts Rózsa: Op. 26a Overture to a Symphony Concert, Op. 14 Three Hungarian Sketches, Op. 28 Notturna Ungherese, Op. 13 Theme, Variations and Finale, 1965; RCA Victor LSC 2802 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa, Spohr, Tchaikovsky, Heifetz, 1956; RCA Victor LM 2027 (Oversize 351)
    - Rózsa, Spohr, Tchaikovsky, Heifetz, 1956; RCA Victor LM 2027 (Oversize 351)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah, 1963; RCA Victor LSO 1076 (Oversize 351)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah, Japan, RVC Corporation CR 10023 (Oversize 351)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah (Sodoma e Gomorra), Italy, 1987; Legend DLD 1-2 (Oversize 351)
    - Sodom and Gomorrah (Sodoma y Gomorra), Spain, 1981; RCA NL 43755 (Oversize 351)
    - Sonata for Piano, 1950; Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 351)
    - Spellbound, REM LP-1 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound, "Instrumental Fox Trot", Decca 73438 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound, Concerto and Red House, Themes, Capitol Records L453 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound, Four-Album Soundtrack, 1945; ARA A-2 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound, Four-Album Soundtrack, 1945; ARA A-2 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound, Ron Goodwin & His Orchestra, England, 1973; EMI Records TWOX 1007 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound and other Classic Film Scores, 1975; RCA ARL1 0911 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound as performed by Heindorf, 1958; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. BS 1213 (Oversize 352)
    - Spellbound as performed by Heindorf, 1958; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. BS 1213 (Oversize 352)
    - [The] Squeaker, 1942 (Oversize 352)
    - Starlight Chorale, Capitol SP 8390 (Oversize 352)
    - Starlight Encores, Hollywood Bowl Symphony Orchestra, Capitol Records P8296 (Oversize 352)
    - Starlight Fantasy, 1961; Capitol SP 28553 (Oversize 352)
    - Stephen Foster, "Massa's in De Cold, Cold Ground" and "Old Black Joe", Tech-Art Recordings (Oversize 352)
    - Thief of Baghdad Suite, Electro-Vox Recording Studios (Oversize 352)
    - Thief of Baghdad, 1977; Film Music Collection BSK 3183 (Oversize 352)
    - Time After Time, 1979; Entr'acte Recording Society ERS 6517 (Oversize 352)
    - Time Out Of Mind, "Concerto", 1947; Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 352)
    - Time Out of Mind, "New England Symphony", Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Oversize 352)
    - To Everything There Is a Season, Dot DLP 3304 (Oversize 352)
    - To Everything There Is a Season, Audiodisc Recording Blank (Oversize 352)
    - [The] V.I.P.s, MGM E4152 ST (Oversize 352)
    - Victory Parade, MGM Pictures (Oversize 352)
    - Warsaw Concerto & other favorite showpieces for piano and orchestra, Angel S36062 (Oversize 352)
- Non-commercial recordings
  - Audiotapes
    This series contains audiotapes (mostly 1/4" reels). Audiotapes are boxed, and should be requested by title, box, and ID number. For example, for the first item below, ask for "3 Hungarian Sketches, Op. 14 [Part 1 and 2], Oversize 360, item rozsa_174."
    Researcher access to recordings requires advance notice in order to produce a working copy.
    - 3 Hungarian Sketches, Op. 14 [Part 1 and 2], rozsa_174; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - 3 Hungarian Sketches, Op.14 [Part 3], rozsa_176; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - A Mass, A Jazzed-Up Version of the V.I.P.’s, rozsa_044; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Alexander Korda Program, rozsa_100; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - The American Youth Symphony Sinfonia Concertante, Op. 29, for Violon, Violoncello, and Orchestra, 2/6/1972; rozsa_133; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Arabic Music Festival, rozsa_013; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Background to Violence, The Naked City, rozsa_167; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Beauty and Grace, 6/11/1959; rozsa_169; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - [Ben Hur] Arrius’ Party Music, rozsa_106; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Ben Hur: Overture, Star of Bethlehem, Gratus' Entry to Jerusalem, The House of Hur, Messala's Revenge, Fertility Dance, Farewell to Rome, Arrius' Party, rozsa_165; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:04 (Oversize 359)
    - Ben Hur: Parade of the Charioteers, Bread & Circus March, Death of Messala, Memories, Sermon on the Mount, Valley of the Dead, Alleluia, rozsa_164; 1/4 inch audio cassette; running time 19:52 (Oversize 359)
    - Ben Hur Album IV. 13 [14 tracks], 10/22/1959; rozsa_178; Copy of original. Side one: prelude, Adoration of the Magi, Roman March, Friendship, Love theme of Ben Hur, The burning desert, The rowing of the Galley Slaves. Side two Noaval Battle, Return to Judia, Victory Parade, The Mother's love, The Leper's search for Christ, Procession to Calvary, The Miracle and Finale].; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Ben Hur Album IV. 13 [14 tracks] [empty reel in box], rozsa_180; Empty reel. Tape transferred to rozsa_178; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Ben Hur Album IV. 14 [14 tracks], Oct 26-28, 1959; rozsa_179; Side one: Prelude, Adoration of the Magi, Roman March, Friendship, Love theme of Ben Hur, The burning desert, Rowing of the galley slaves. Side two: Naval battle, Return to Judea, Victory Parade, The mother's love, The leper's search for Christ, The procession to Calvary, The Miracal and Finale]; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Ben Hur Album IV. 14 [14 tracks] [empty reel in box], Oct 26-28, 1959; rozsa_181; Empty reel. Tape transferred to rozsa_179; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Blind Flight, rozsa_160; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Brute Force, rozsa_228; Disc No. 6234, production No. 1537. Main titles; Fur Coat Scene; Italian Scene; Ruth and Joe; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Side 1: 1A-4C; Side 2: 6C-7B
    - Cantata Faust et Helene, 3/24/1975; rozsa_098; Performed by Lyne Dourian, Jose Tudarre, Robert Massart, l’orchestre Radio-Lyrique. Conducted by J.P. Marty.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Canto di Natale, 1974; rozsa_027; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [illegible] Cello and Orchestra, Op. 32, rozsa_194; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Circus Parade; Gratus Entry; Victory Finale; Victory Parade (Short Version), 10/2/1959; rozsa_185; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 8:45 (Oversize 361)
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, rozsa_116; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:30 (Oversize 359)
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, Munich, rozsa_107; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra Op. 31, 9/28/1968; rozsa_086; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, Op. 31, rozsa_136; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, Op. 31 [missing], rozsa_154; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Concerto for String Orchestra Op. 17, rozsa_009; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Concerto for String Orchestra Op. 17, rozsa_093; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Concerto for String Orchestra, Op. 17, 3/30/1958; rozsa_172; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Concerto for String Orchestra, Op. 17; Kaleidoscope, Op. 19a; Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song for Violin and Orchestra, Op. 1; Denes Zsigmony, Violin with the Vienna State Opera Orchestra, rozsa_051; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Concerto for Strings, 5/1/1951; rozsa_197; 1st, 2nd and 3rd movements; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 362)
    - Concerto for Strings, First Movement (takes 1 and 2), rozsa_190; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Concerto for Strings, Second Movement (takes 2 and 3), 5/1/1951; rozsa_189; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Concerto for Strings, Third Movement (takes 1 and 2), 5/7/1951; rozsa_188; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Concerto for Strings, San Francisco Concert, Op. 17, 12/15/1957; rozsa_173; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Concerto for Violin & Orchestra, Op. 24, 1/15/1956; rozsa_045; Performance at McFarlin Memorial Auditorium in Dallas, Texas; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Concerto for Violin and Orchestra Op. 24, rozsa_186; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Concerto for Violoncello & Orchestra, Op. 32 [missing], 3/20-22, 1974; rozsa_050; Baverian Symphony Orchestra, Munich; Cello, Janos Starker; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Concerto for Violoncello and Orchestra, rozsa_026; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Concerto for Violoncello and Orchestra, Janos Starker, Cello with the Sacramento Symphony Orchestra and Harry Newstone as conductor; rozsa_046; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Daniel Robbins String Quartet, rozsa_006; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - [Demonstration] with Walter Rubsamen, Gerhart Albersheim, and Miklos Rozsa, rozsa_049; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - [Discussion, untitled], Moderator: Miklos Rozsa, Guests: Andre Previn, Raymond Kendall, Bronislau Kaper, John Crown; rozsa_147; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Duo for Cello and Piano, Op. 8 and Piano Sonata, Op. 20, rozsa_157; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Duo for Violin and Piano Performed by Manuel and Sara Compinsky, rozsa_065; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Duo for Violin and Piano, Op. 7 Performed by Manuel and Sara Compinsky, rozsa_132; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Duo Toccata [missing], rozsa_148; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - El Cid [Part 1], 12/24/1961; rozsa_171; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:20 (Oversize 360)
    - El Cid [Part 2], 12/31/1961; rozsa_170; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - Eye of the Needle #1, rozsa_112; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Eye of the Needle #2, rozsa_134; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Eye of the Needle #3, rozsa_124; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Fedora Score, Roll 1, rozsa_058; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Fedora Score, Roll 2, rozsa_059; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 357)
    - Film Music, rozsa_092; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - Film Music of Miklos Rozsa and Christopher Palmer, rozsa_096; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:30 (Oversize 358)
    - Film Music Voc 2, Oct 1975; rozsa_187; Knight without Armour; Tribute to a Bad Man; Asrmalt Jungle; Moon Fleet; Double in Demnity; Lust for Life; "Blind Flight"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - First Hearing, 12/20/1978; rozsa_109; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 358)
    - The Four Feathers, Korda, London Films, rozsa_151; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 360)
    - France Musique Interview, rozsa_193; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 361)
    - Frankisches Landesorchester Nurnberg (Telefon 30956, Bucher Strasse 137) Three Hungarian Sketches, rozsa_017; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Franz Schubert’s Symphony No. 8 in B Minor, 11/26/1957; rozsa_138; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)
    - Glendale Symphony Orchestra, 12/18/1960; rozsa_024; Ben Hur (?)- First Half of Broadcast; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 356)
    - Glendale Symphony Orchestra [first half of broadcast], 12/18/1960; rozsa_130; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 359)